<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="SIGN_CONTRACT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You sign the contract.
	</p>
	<p>
		Mistress Yui commands you to strip and change into your pink latex outfit.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="STRIP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You strip and put on the latex outfit.
	</p>
	<p>
		Mistress uses webbing to tie you up and spread your legs. She stuffs a huge dildo in your pussy/ass.
	</p>
	<p>
		As the toy begins to vibrate, she says to wait like a good toy until the day's finished.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WAIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You spend the rest of the day tied up with vibrating toys in ass/pussy. Cumming over and over again, members of the public comment on your lewd display.
	</p>
	<p>
		Unlike the last time you were wearing this getup, you're not blindfolded nor gagged, and you moan in shameful delight as you see members to the public pointing and commenting on you.
	</p>
	<p>
		You're led back to Mistress Yui's home.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Arrive home. Inside, luxurious lounge with BDSM accessories on the walls. Further inspection reveals anchor points on the leather sofas and rings on the ceiling.
	</p>
	<p>
		A bimbo greater wolf-tauress is furiously slamming back against the wall, and as she rushes forwards to greet Yui, you see a gigantic, sopping-wet dildo flop down.
	</p>
	<p>
		Suddenly, a pair of voices speak as one from behind you, and you turn to see androgynous lamia twins. Their scales and skin are white, and their pixie-cut hair, lipstick, nail polish, and eye-shadow are neon blue.
	</p>
	<p>
		Finally, a male arachne makes an appearance. Jet-black chitin and skin, heavily pierced with gold, a huge, precum-drooling cock extends from beneath his spider body.
	</p>
	<p>
		Yui says that you're a super submissive slut who'd love to serve her toys.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BROKEN_IN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Bimbo wolf-tauress pounces on you and face-sits. Her big, sloppy, musky cunt covers your face, and you eat her out as she moans.
	</p>
	<p>
		The lamia twins constrict you. Their cocks tease at your pussy/ass/mouth. Get fucked while they make out with each other.
	</p>
	<p>
		Arachne ties you up and spanks hard. Makes you squeal then rams huge dildo in your ass/pussy.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_FUCKED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Yui returns. Tells you all to get cleaned up as clients will arrive in 30 mins.
	</p>
	<p>
		Shower and change into clean latex outfit.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FINAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Clients arrive and fuck you all. This is your life, as a slave to Yui. Used by her other toys and clients. Only time you're not engaged in kinky sex is while sleeping, and even then sometimes you're used.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
