<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that Fia is going to be in one of the many bars near here, you start to walk up and down the street, peering through windows as you search for her. After just a few minutes, you see the reporter in an upmarket cocktail bar with a drink in her hand. Entering the establishment, you [pc.walk] over to the bar and say hello to your friend.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech([pc.Name]!)] she happily greets you with a big smile on her face. Gesturing for you to sit down, she calls out to the donkey-boy barman, [fia.speech(Hey, Frank! Put another whiskey on my tab, would you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you sit down next to Fia, a glass of whiskey is placed down on the bartop in front of you. Thanking her for the drink, you ask her how she's been.
	</p>
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_inky_obtained))
		<p>
			[fia.speech(I'm doing great, thanks,)] she happily replies. Taking a sip of her own whiskey, she asks, [fia.speech(So, what's up?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[fia.speech(Well, I've been kind of scared of Sae as I thought she'd try to get revenge on me. I've been hiding from her by staying with some family, which was fun,)] she replies, before revealing, [fia.speech(Thankfully my editor went and spoke to Sae on my behalf, and apparently she isn't at all interested in getting revenge on me, so I've moved back to my apartment. My editor's the best ever. Oh! That reminds me! She made something for you!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You're surprised to hear that Fia's editor has sent you a gift, and watch with curiosity as Fia reaches into her hoodie's pocket and pulls out a small object. As she presents it to you, you see that the gift is a fancy-looking fountain pen.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like you've spent enough time with Fia, you tell her that it was nice seeing her again, but you've got places to be.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(It was great seeing you too, [pc.name],)] she replies with a smile on her face. Finishing off the last of her drink, she says, [fia.speech(I'd better get going now too. I've got some leads to follow up on.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you exit the bar together, and after saying a final goodbye, you set off in different directions. Wandering down the street past Lovienne's Luxuries, you wonder what to do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="TALK_SMALL_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to take this opportunity to just relax for a while and make some small talk, you tell Fia that you approve of her hangout spot.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Yeah, the bars around here are great,)] she replies, [fia.speech(I've got loads of contacts in Demon Home, so hanging out in these places is as much work as it is pleasure.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		From there, the two of you talk about Demon Home and Dominion in general, before sharing some experiences you've recently had in the city. The time flies by as you talk, and before you know it you've spent almost half an hour chatting with one another.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although not much of substance was said by either of you, you feel like the two of you have got to know each other a little better. As Fia pauses to take a sip of her drink, you wonder what to say next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="TALK_BACKGROUND"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious to hear more about Fia's background, you ask her how she came to be a reporter.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Well, my first job was as a barmaid in one of the bars on the other side of Demon Home,)] she reveals, [fia.speech(I loved getting stories out of the customers, and after a while I decided to write a book about all the fun things I'd heard. Well, it turns out that nobody wants to publish demons' spicy secrets and risk pissing off an important succubus, so that went nowhere. After getting rejected by every publisher in the Realm, I decided to try my luck at the offices of The Octogram Herald.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Recognising that name as that of the only newspaper in Dominion, you can guess the rest of Fia's story, and ask her if that's when she was hired as a journalist.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(That's right,)] she replies, [fia.speech(They were so impressed with all the gossip and contacts I'd gathered that I was offered a job as a permanent reporter on the affairs of Demon Home. And I've been working there ever since!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With Fia's history now revealed, you wonder what to ask her about next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="TALK_NEWSPAPER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From what you've gathered during your time in Dominion, the newspaper which Fia works for is the only official source of news for the city. Wanting to find out more about what it's like to work for such a company, you ask the reporter what she can tell you about it.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Well, everyone's heard of The Octogram Herald, of course, but I guess not many people know what it's really like,)] she muses, before revealing, [fia.speech(I'm an investigate reporter who specialises in Demon Home, but there are loads of different departments, and our editor oversees all of them. She's super nice and works non-stop, and even though she's one of the highest-ranking lilin in all the Realm, she really cares about us and takes the time to get to know us all. Anyway, it's thanks to her high status that we're able to publish negative stories about demons.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You're surprised to hear that the Realm's official news source is printing stories that show demons in a bad light, and express this to Fia.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Well, it's really only lilin and Lilith herself who are off-limits,)] she says,
		#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
			 [fia.speech(You're a demon, so you know how it is. You get access to better jobs and everyone respects you a lot more than other races, but that doesn't make you immune to criticism. So long as we take care not to print anything that might be construed as sedition, we can expose demons' crimes and unfair dealings. In fact, sometimes my editor specifically asks me to dig up a story about a certain demon.)]
		#ELSE
			 [fia.speech(Sure, demons get access to better jobs and everyone respects them a lot more, but that doesn't make them immune to criticism. So long as we take care not to print anything that might be construed as sedition, we can expose demons' crimes and unfair dealings. In fact, sometimes my editor specifically asks me to dig up a story about a certain demon.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		It sounds like the lilin editor of The Octogram Herald is using the newspaper to influence demon politics. Wondering if there's anything else you can find out about it, you ask Fia what other kind of stories they work on.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Just the usual sort of stuff,)] she replies. After taking a sip of her drink, she finishes by saying, [fia.speech(I don't really get involved with any of the other departments, so I can't tell you much.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		It seems like Fia doesn't really have much else to say about her newspaper...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="TALK_STORIES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After finishing the story about Saellatrix and her sex doll factory, you wonder if Fia's already working on something else, and so you ask her what she's investigating at the moment.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(I've got a few leads on some scandals involving demons, but nothing even close to what Sae was up to,)] she reveals, before suddenly asking, [fia.speech(Hey, have you ever been down to Submission?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You tell Fia that you've been down to Submission multiple times, and have experienced enough dark, dangerous tunnels to last you a lifetime.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(That's great!)] she happily exclaims, before explaining, [fia.speech(Look, I only work here in Demon Home, but my editor's asked everyone to try and get some stories on Submission. Apparently there's a growing interest in what's happening beneath our feet, but we haven't really got anything to report on from down there. If you've got some juicy stories to share, I can pay you five thousand flames for each of them. Or perhaps...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Fia's words trail off, and she flashes you a rather seductive smile. Playfully teasing one of her fingers through her [fia.hairColour] hair, she gives you a smouldering look and lewdly suggests,
		#IF(fia.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0)
			 [fia.speech(Perhaps instead of money you'd like to fuck me like you did back in Sae's factory... I can't stop thinking about that, you know...)]
		#ELSE
			 [fia.speech(Perhaps instead of money you'd like to fuck me...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Picking up her glass, Fia takes a sip of her drink and gives you a big smile as she waits to hear what you'll say next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WHISKEY_SIP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.random(
		Taking this opportunity to relax and have a drink, you take a sip of your whiskey while Fia makes some small talk about how her day's been.
		|
		Turning your attention to the drink that's in front of you, you take a sip of whiskey while Fia tells you about what she's been up to today.
		|
		Picking up your glass of whiskey, you take a sip and relax as Fia idly talks about some of the things she's been up to today.
		)]
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'><i>
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('fia_whiskey_sips')==1)
			Your glass is still mostly full...
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('fia_whiskey_sips')==2)
			You've still got a lot of whiskey left in your glass...
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('fia_whiskey_sips')==3)
			Your glass is less than half-full now...
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('fia_whiskey_sips')==4)
			You've only got a little whiskey left in your glass...
		#ELSE
			[style.colourMinorBad(Your glass is now empty...)]
		#ENDIF
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WHISKEY_ORDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As your whiskey has run out, you get the attention of the donkey-boy barman and order another drink. As Fia paid for your first drink, you offer to return the favour and buy a drink for her, but she lifts up her half-full glass and smiles to indicate that she doesn't need another one.
	</p>
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_fia_bar_alcohol_refused))
		<p>
			A moment later, the barman is placing another glass of whiskey down in front of you. With your head starting to spin from the alcohol in your system, it takes you three attempts to slide the glass closer to you. Watching your uncoordinated movements, the barman lets out the briefest of grunts, before shaking his head and saying in a firm tone, [style.speechMasculineHeavy(I can see that you've had enough, so this is your last drink for tonight.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the donkey-boy turns away and slowly walks down to another part of the bar, leaving you and Fia to continue your conversation in peace.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			A moment later, the barman is placing another glass of whiskey down in front of you. With the briefest of nods, he turns away and slowly walks down to another part of the bar, leaving you and Fia to continue your conversation in peace.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="STORY_SLIME_QUEEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to tell Fia one of your stories from Submission, you ask her if she's heard of the slime queen, Catherine, before.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Oh, right, I heard from an Enforcer that she was behind the increase in slimes, but apparently she's been stopped,)] she says, before asking, [fia.speech(Did you have something to do with that?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slimeQueenHelped))
			Deciding to leave out the part where you chose to assist Catherine instead of putting an end to her activities, you tell Fia the same account which you gave to Claire. 
		#ELSE
			Teling Fia that you were the one responsible for putting an end to Catherine's activities, you give her your account of what happened.
		#ENDIF
		 After discovering that the slime queen was responsible for the aggressive slimes in the tunnels of Submission, you tracker her down to a tower on an island deep within the Bat Caverns. After encountering a pair of slime twins, and then a guard who wielded a fearsome zweihander, you encountered the huge, pink slime queen herself. After defeating her, you returned her crown to Claire as proof of your deed, and with that Catherine's plan to flood Submission with slimes was ended.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="STORY_VENGAR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to tell Fia a story about Submission, you ask her if she's heard about Vengar's gang before.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(The rat-boy, right?)] she asks. As you give Fia a nod, she recalls, [fia.speech(His gang was raided by SWORD, wasn't it? I'm pretty sure that one of the other departments ran a story on that, but the Enforcers wouldn't share many details... You know something more about it?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Fia that you were the one responsible for bringing Vengar down, you wait while she fishes her notepad and pen out of her hoodie's pocket before launching into your story. Beginning with your encounter with Roxy in Axel's gambling den, you describe how you set off to the Rat Warrens to put an end to Vengar's extortion of Axel's business.
		#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_VENGAR, QUEST_VENGAR_TWO_ENFORCERS))
			 Recounting how you used a resonance stone to call for the SWORD Enforcers, you finish your tale by saying that you were assisted by two rat-girls named Shadow and Silence.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_VENGAR, QUEST_VENGAR_TWO_COOPERATION))
			 Recounting how you decided to cooperate with Vengar, you say that 
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_axelSissified))
				 Axel ended up being feminised before
			#ELSE
				 you and Axel confronted the rat-boy, before
			#ENDIF
			 SWORD Enforcers launched their raid, and during the chaos you were assisted by two rat-girls named Shadow and Silence.
		#ELSE
			 Recounting how you had to use violence to bring an end to Vengar's reign, you recount how you fought his bodyguards, Shadow and Silence, who later turned out to be working with the SWORD Enforcers.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="STORY_HLF_BASE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that Fia might be interested in hearing about that artificial cave you discovered in the Bat Caverns, you ask her if she's ever heard of crazy people living down there.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Crazy people down in the Bat Caverns?)] she wonders out loud, before humming and saying, [fia.speech(Well, there are those bat-morphs who just love talking, and I've heard that there are some weird glowing slimes down there. Why? What did you find?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You recount how you discovered the lever which granted access to a hidden cave deep within the Bat Caverns, and describe how the derelict interior was on the verge of collapsing. You cautiously travelled through this subterranean lair and discovered a crazy, partially-transformed human who attacked you on sight. The journal which you found after that described a rebellion starting in 1988, and after three years of fighting against the Enforcers, the writer said that a supposed angel named Astrea caused their group to fracture and split apart.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(That must have been from the Fifth Human Rebellion!)] Fia exclaims, [fia.speech(There was still a rebel down there?! It was all way before my time, but in our offices we've got front pages from those times framed and hanging on the walls.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your story not yet finished, you tell Fia that had a narrow escape as you exited the cave, for it completely collapsed right behind you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="STORY_GENERIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You don't have any more interesting stories about Submission, but you want to help Fia out, and so you tell her about some of your recent adventures and ask if they're of any use to her.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="INKY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking the pen from her, you turn it over in your [pc.hands] and take a closer look at it. The quality is immediately apparent, and you get the feeling that it's a very expensive item of stationary. As you start to thank Fia, you suddenly detect a tiny tremor of arcane power, and so after expressing your gratitude, you make the comment that there's something more to this pen than meets the eye. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(That's right! I was wondering if you could tell, but I guess nothing gets past you, huh?)] she laughs, before revealing, [fia.speech(I don't think I've told you before, but my editor's a lilin; she's a daughter of the elder lilins Lovienne and Lirecea. So, as you'd guess, she's pretty amazing at harnessing the arcane. After I told her about what we went through in the sex doll factory, she made a dozen of those pens and gave them to all of us investigative reporters. If we get in trouble, we can use the pen's enchantment to help us out!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling off the cap, you take a closer look at the nib and then within the cap itself. Although you can still faintly detect an arcane presence within the pen, there's nothing about it to suggest that it'd be of any use in a fight.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(I'll tell you how to use it, but don't activate it in here, ok?)] Fia says, [fia.speech(So, all you need to do is twist the cap three times and then pull it off. When that happens, an arcane entity gets summoned which will distract anyone who's harassing or attacking you. As you'd expect from a daughter of Lirecea, who from what I hear spends all of her time in the form of an octopus-girl, the arcane entity looks like a little octopus. She named them all 'Inky', and they're kind of lewd, but I guess that's what's to be expected from a lilin, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Fia to pass your thanks along to her editor, you put the pen somewhere safe and make a mental note to take a closer look at it later.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(So, what's up?)] she happily asks as she takes a sip of her drink.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORY_END"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_fia_stories_complete))
		<p>
			[fia.speech(Well, there's no doubt that you have a lot of interesting stories,)] Fia says, but then with a shake of her head she sighs, [fia.speech(I'm sorry, but they're not enough for me to write an article on. I can't offer you the five thousand flames for this, but I wouldn't want you to leave empty-handed...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Fia's slender fingers are suddenly tracing over your hips, and with a little giggle she teases, [fia.speech(How about the two of us have some fun together? This place has a couple of rooms to rent for customers who need some privacy...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[fia.speech(This is gold! It's exactly the sort of story which I was looking for,)] Fia happily exclaims as she finishes jotting down all the details in her notebook. Suddenly giving you a sly look, she teases, [fia.speech(So, do you want the five thousand flames? Or is it me that you want instead? This place has a couple of rooms to rent for customers who need some privacy...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Fia's slender fingers are suddenly tracing over your hips, and with a little giggle she playfully bites her lip and waits to hear what reward you'll choose...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORY_SEX_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You don't really want to have sex with Fia, and so turn her down by saying that you've got somewhere else to be tonight. Playfully pouting at you, she whines, [fia.speech(Aww... Well, maybe next time then?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving her a non-committal response, you stand up and say that it was nice seeing her again.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(It was great seeing you too, [pc.name],)] she replies with a smile on her face. Finishing off the last of her drink, she says, [fia.speech(I guess I should get going now too. I've got some leads to follow up on.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you exit the bar together, and after saying a final goodbye, you set off in different directions. Wandering down the street past Lovienne's Luxuries, you wonder what to do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="STORY_REWARD_FLAMES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding the five thousand flames to be the more attractive reward, you tell Fia that you'd like the money. Smirking as she places the coins down on the bar in front of you, she teases, [fia.speech(Well, maybe next time you'll choose me?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving her a non-committal response, you pocket the money and ask her what she's planning to do for the rest of the evening.
	</p>
	<p>
		Finishing off the last of her drink, she says, [fia.speech(Well, I've got some leads to follow up on, and I should go and get this story of yours written up, so I'd better be going.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your companion leaving, you decide to head out as well, and so the two of you exit the bar together. After saying goodbye, you each set off in different directions. Wandering down the street past Lovienne's Luxuries, you wonder what to do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="SEX_OPTIONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing exactly which reward you'd prefer, you tell Fia that you can't resist her sexy body. Finishing off her drink, she jumps to her feet and grabs your [pc.arm(true)] before giggling, [fia.speech(I was hoping you'd choose me! Come on, [pc.name]!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling the barman to put the room's rent on her tab, Fia leads you through a door and up a flight of stairs. Pushing open another door, she pulls you into an average-sized bedroom that's light on furnishings but clean and tidy. The king-sized bed has red sheets and heart-shaped pillows, and there's a bowl of condoms on the bedside table.
	</p>
	<p>
		Locking the door behind you, Fia kicks off her boots and skips forwards to excitedly jump onto the bed. Turning to face you with a huge smile on her face, she says, [fia.speech(You can fuck me however you like, but my pussy is off-limits! I'm saving my virginity, and all this immediately ends if you even try to touch it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that rule having been clearly expressed, Fia pulls off her hoodie and tank top, leaving her wearing just her sports bra, daisy dukes, and socks. Continuing to smile, she waits to see what you'll do with her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEX_OPTIONS_TAKE_CONDOMS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to be prepared for what's about to happen, you quickly grab a few condoms from one of the bowls beside the bed...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="FIA_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Eager to get things started, you join Fia on the bed and dominantly pull her into you as she giggles and plants a kiss on your [pc.lips+]. After lustfully grinding her body against your for a moment, she lies back on the bed and giggles, [fia.speech(Fuck me, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="FIA_SEX_START_INTERCRURAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The fact that she doesn't want her pussy penetrated just makes Fia's virgin cunt even more enticing, and so you tell her that you want to fuck her tight, wet twat more than anything else.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(Absolutely not,)] she firmly replies, before flashing you a smirk and saying, [fia.speech(But if you're so desperate to fuck me... Get your cock out.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hoping that she's going to let you take her virginity, you quickly present Fia with your erect cock as she pulls off her daisy dukes and boyshorts and throws them over to one side of the room. Pushing herself up onto all fours, she wiggles her ass at you and giggles, [fia.speech(You're not going to fuck me, but I'll let you pretend. Bring that cock over here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			Swiftly mounting Fia,
		#ELSE
			Swiftly dropping down behind Fia,
		#ENDIF
		 you line your cock up to her virgin cunt, but before you can even think of penetrating her, she reaches back with one hand and firmly grabs your rock-hard shaft. With your dick now completely under her control, Fia playfully slides the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock up and down over her [fia.labia+], moaning as she does so, [fia.speech(You want my hot little pussy? Your cock feels good rubbing against my virgin cunt? Sorry, [pc.name]... You can't have it! But here's the next best thing...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving her knees together so that they're touching, Fia's thighs are squished up against each other, and she moves your cock down to the crevice that's formed and loosens her grip. Turned on and desperate to sink your cock into her, you immediately thrust forwards, and as your [pc.cock+] pushes in-between Fia's soft thighs, you feel her wet pussy kissing the top of your shaft. Trusting you not to penetrate her pussy, Fia lets go of your cock, and as you continue fucking her thighs, she lewdly moans,
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 [fia.speech(~Mmm!~ If this isn't enough for you, then just stick it in my ass!)]
		#ELSE
			 [fia.speech(~Mmm!~ If this isn't enough for you, then you can always just fuck my throat!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Keeping Fia's offer in mind, you decide to continue fucking her thighs for the time being...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(fia.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			[fia.speech(Fuck, that was amazing,)] Fia sighs as she collapses back onto the bed, panting for breath.
		#ELSE
			[fia.speech(You could have at least tried to satisfy me, [pc.name],)] Fia complains as you bring an end to the sex.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After taking a couple of minutes to recover, the two of you get your things back in order, and as you look at the mess the two of you have made of the bed, Fia says, [fia.speech(The cleanup cost is included in what I paid to rent this room, so just leave it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After pulling on her boots and hoodie, your companion is once again fully dressed, and happily skips over to the door. As you join her, she unlocks it and leads you back down to the bar.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had a lot of fun with her, you tell Fia that it was great seeing her again, and you hope to catch her here again some other time.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fia.speech(It was great seeing you too, [pc.name],)] she replies with a smile on her face. Accompanying you as you head over to the door, she says, [fia.speech(I've got some leads to follow up on tonight... My work never ends!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you exit the bar together, and after saying a final goodbye, you set off in different directions. Wandering down the street past Lovienne's Luxuries, you wonder what to do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>